Guide to the Benjamin Sussman Papers, 1940-1995
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- N: Entertainment/Amusements, (4 boxes)
  - N-418: Ice shows (Box 42)
  - N-419: Industrial theatre (Box 42)
  - N-420-422: Reviews, A-L (Box 42)
  - N-423-428: Reviews, M-Z and miscellaneous (Box 43)
  - N-500: Music, general (Box 43)
  - N-501: Music, historical (Box 43)
  - N-502: Composers, conductors (Box 43)
  - N-503: Musicians (Box 43)
  - N-504: Opera (Box 43)
  - N-505: Symphonies (Box 43)
  - N-506: Folk music (Box 43)
  - N-507: Ragtime (Box 43)
  - N-508: Pop music (Box 43)
  - N-509: Dance bands (Box 43)
  - N-510: Marching bands (Box 43)
  - N-511: Instruments, general (Box 43)
  - N-512: Pianos (Box 43)
  - N-513: Player pianos (Box 43)
  - N-514: Organs (Box 43)
  - N-515: Jukeboxes (Box 43)
  - N-516: Record industry (Box 43)
  - N-517: Recording, general (Box 44)
  - N-518: Cassettes, tapes (Box 44)
  - N-519: Plugging, Payola (Box 44)
  - N-520: Piracy (Box 44)
  - N-521: Propaganda, controversy (Box 44)
- O: Holidays/Celebrations, (1 box)
  - O-100: Holidays/celebrations, general (Box 44)
  - O-101: Armed Forces Day (Box 44)
  - O-102: Christmas (Box 44)
  - O-104: Easter (Box 44)
  - O-105: Fathers Day (Box 44)
  - O-106: Halloween (Box 44)
  - O-107: Independence Day/July 4th (Box 44)
  - O-108: Labor Day (Box 44)
  - O-109: Lent (Box 44)
  - O-110: Lincoln's birthday (Box 44)
  - O-111: Mardis Gras (Box 44)
  - O-112: Memorial Day (Box 44)
  - O-113: Mothers Day (Box 44)
  - O-114: New Years Day (Box 44)
  - O-115: Passover (Box 44)
  - O-116: St. Patrick's Day (Box 44)
  - O-117: Thanksgiving (Box 44)
  - O-118: St. Valentine's Day (Box 44)
  - O-119: Veterans Day (Box 44)
  - O-120: Washington's Birthday (Box 44)
- P: Production Sources, (2 boxes)
  - P-100: Production sources, misc. (Box 44)
  - P-101: Art supplies, equip. (Box 44)
  - P-102: Office supplies (Box 44)
  - P-103: Office equipment (Box 44)
  - P-104: Audio/visual equipment (Box 44)
  - P-105: Printers (3 folders) (Box 44)
  - P-107a: Leather goods, binders (Box 44)
  - P-109: Mailing houses (Box 44)
  - P-112: Typographers (Box 44)
  - P-113: Advertising specialties (4 folders) (Box 44)
  - P-114: Packaging (Box 44)
  - P-115: Displays, exhibits (Box 44)
  - P-115a: Point of purchase (Box 45)
  - P-116: Signs (Box 45)
  - P-117: Plaques (Box 45)
  - P-118: Trophies (Box 45)
  - P-119: Badges, buttons, ribbons (Box 45)
  - P-120: Balloons (Box 45)
  - P-121: Modelmaking (Box 45)
  - P-122: Puppets, miniatures (Box 45)
  - P-123: Industrial designers (Box 45)
  - P-125: Artists (Box 45)
  - P-126: Art studios (Box 45)
  - P-127: Photographers (Box 45)
  - P-128: Stock photos (Box 45)
  - P-129: Photostats, resolutions (Box 45)
  - P-130: Photo processing (Box 45)
  - P-131: Murals (Box 45)
  - P-132: Old photos, prints (Box 45)
  - P-133: Quantity photos (Box 45)
  - P-134: Props, costumes (Box 45)
  - P-135: TV/film production (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - P-136: Models, male (Box 45)
  - P-137: Models, female (Box 45)
  - P-138: Personnel, misc. (4 folders) (Box 45)